You have to be in better shape than that.
你必须比现在身材更好.
Carl, it was heavy.
Carl, 它很重.
That's why you need stamina and strength.
这就是为什么你需要耐力和力气.
Look at me.
看看我.
I work out in a gym three times a week,
我一个星期去健身房三次.
because the job demands it.
因为工作需要.
You do that for work?
你那么做是为了工作?
Absolutely.
当然了.
Carl, we do that at work.
Carl,我们工作时就在那么做了.
We don't sit at a desk all day.
我们没有坐在办工桌前一整天.
We don't stare at a computer for hours.
我们没有盯着电脑几个小时
We're active. Isn't that enough?
我们是在活动的. 那还不够吗?
I quit smoking.
我戒了烟.
I eat healthy, balanced meals.
我吃健康 营养均衡的食物.
I sleep eight hours a night.
我一晚上睡八个小时.
I am the picture of health, Peter.
我是健康的化身, Peter.
That means I do a better job.
那意味着我工作的更好.
Oh boy.
Hey. Watch and learn.
Hey. 看着学.